So a few days ago I
posted on the YouTube community that
my Ola S1 Pro had met with a minor
accident and I had to file an insurance claim for it.
How much did I have to pay for it, how much time did it take,
I am going to share everything with you guys in today's video.
If
such an incident happens to you too, then
this video is going to be very helpful for you guys,
so
definitely watch the video till the end and if you are visiting the channel for the first
time, then please subscribe to the channel. Do
press the gas button. Just last week,
when I was going somewhere on my Ola scooter,
someone hit my scooter from behind on the roadside. I did
n't suffer much damage, but the
part below the oil light of the scooter and
some scratches appeared on the side. Then I
talked to Ola customer care support for this
and registered a complaint. But after two days
I got a call back. They said that
we cannot repair your scooter at home,
you will have to bring it to the service center
which is in Delhi.  I went there
and submitted the scooter there, a
complete inspection of the scooter was done, the
insurance team came there, they saw
how much damage was there in the scooter, how many
parts would have to be replaced, and everything was
asked about how it happened, and
then
this scooter was given to the insurance department for further process,
I had taken Euroder insurance from ICC Lombard company on this scooter,
for which
I knew that I would not have to pay any penalty,
and this is what happened, so first of all
they asked me for a copy of the insurance,
which is already there in my Ola application,
so I sent it to them quickly,
then they asked me for RC DL, Aadhar
card, PAN card, insurance policy claim
number with full form,
which I
provided to them as quickly as possible, here you will get a lab
number from the customer care of the insurance company,
and the
insurance company will
give you a link to the claim form, in which you have to fill the full form and give it to
them, so the
sooner you provide all these documents to them,
the faster your loan
process will move forward.  I
provided them all the documents within a maximum of one hour.
After that, my case was registered and
next day, the scooter was surveyed.
After the survey, an approval has to be taken
which takes 24 to 48 hours to
come, that is, it took 2 days to
come and by Wednesday evening, my scooter was
completely fitted to me, that is,
they changed all the parts etc.,
the approval etc. was done, so let me tell you what all
changes have happened in my scooter here.
Its oil light has been changed here, which
was for Rs. 358. The panel below the oil light has been changed, which was for
Rs. 995. The upper panel has been changed,
which is for Rs. 2953. The rear
fender has also been changed, which is for Rs. 722. So,
my total bill here was
Rs. 837. For this, labour charges etc. are all included
in it. Apart from this, I also paid Rs.  But I
paid a little, that is,
I paid ₹377 for the screw, etc. file charges,
so if
seen overall, the insurance of Icon company here is
quite good, there is
no need to pay police etc. here and
their process is also done very quickly.
Otherwise, if you get into such a situation, then
definitely file a police complaint for
your safety. Many times, there are such
insurance companies which
ask for such things, so you will have to pay them on time.
Next, whenever you
go to make a claim like this, you should go on weekdays only
or if you go on Monday, then you will get
more money because
approval does not come on weekends. If it is Saturday or
Sunday, then there is a holiday here,
after which your insurance
process will move forward, that is,
you will spend two days here, so if possible,
you should go on weekdays only, then there will be more money.
You will
definitely need these documents to make the claim, if you
provide all these documents as soon as possible, then you can get them.  If
you give it, the sooner your claim
process will start, rest fingers
crossed, no one should have all these things,
same friends, my number plate had
fallen off a long time ago, but till now
I have talked to Olasa support for it, but
they have not helped me at all.
Here, I have also talked to
their sales manager at their new showroom, but
he has also not helped me.
I went to the party office, but I could
not find its number plate there at all.
Secondly, I also tried to register on the online search
website, but it did
not happen there either. So, if any of you have
ordered your number plate again, then
please do let me know in the comment box below
because I am not getting its number plate.
Rest friends, if you have seen the
video Infinity, then please
like the video. I will meet you
in the new video, till then, end to fight
[Music]